- Yeah?
- Plane's leaving Miami.
Landing at 9am with six keys of Fentanyl.
- Is the meeting confirmed?
- Looks like it.
I need confirmation.
Lots of strings to pull.
Yeah. Tell me about it!
It's them.
Stay cool. It'll all be all right.
Crazy Heaven club, looking for wife.
- You want to join, huh?
- Thanks. I got one already. Hey, listen.
Why we never go out together, my brother?
Why you didn't have good time with me?
Hey, listen, the plane's landing at nine.
- So you got to sober up, OK?
- All good?
Six passengers.
You're a fucking genius, man.
Tomorrow we sit down with him.
Six passengers
will get my uncle's attention.
All right.
Girls, you tell him to go to bed. OK?
You need to fucking sober up.
I'll pick you up in two hours, OK?
I need you sharp.
I was born sharp, my friend!
- Born sharp as a fucking razor!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Was I talking too loud?
You should tell him there's no bad words
in our house.
You're so right, baby.
You're so right.
Hey, you know that camping trip
that we were talking about before?
- The one just me and Mom?
- Mm-hm. It's tonight.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You want to go wake up Mommy?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, go wake her up!
- Mom, wake up!
Mommy! Mommy, wake up!
- We're going camping!
- It's happening.
You got 20 minutes.
Keep the lights off.
Yeah?
Boss, Koslow is taking us to the General
in the a.m.
We're moving in. I sent you the ops plan.
We need verbal approval.
Give me a sec, Wilcox.
How many bodies you got?
11. Four surveillance, seven arrest team.
You did good.
Koslow was your idea.
You'll get credit for this.
Concur. You're good to go.
Thank you, boss.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
thank you all for coming.
This is Rysard Klimek.
His gang, known as Wojtek,
is one of the major importers
and distributors of Fentanyl,
the new dope sensation among junkies,
also known as pink or synthetic heroin.
We're going after him.
his top drug runner,
who will receive the drugs and take them
to the General at his factory,
providing all the evidence we need
to move in.
Please make a visual note of our source.
And when we move in, go easy on him.
I'll hand over
to the tactical team leader
for the layout of the meat factory
and final brief back.
- Pete, I'm not gonna need that key.
- Hey. Hey. Hey.
You don't open the door to anyone.
- And if I'm not back here by one...
- Pete, stop it.
- ..leave without me.
- I don't want to hear this.
1pm, baby. OK?
You got to promise me.
This time tomorrow, we'll be on the road.
All this will be over.
All right, same as usual.
This is recording now and will be
recording the whole time.
All your private numbers are in there.
Mother, Cousin Jackie, and Dad - it's me.
If I need to communicate,
I will send you WhatsApp messages
using one of these names.
If I call you, don't be surprised.
Just answer.
Before you meet the General,
they'll strip you of all electronics.
This one needs to enter the room.
- The wire's in place.
- Today you need to wear mine.
Hey, it's my ass that's gonna get
pat down. The wire's in place.
All right, let's test it.
You want to turn around, please?
Of course. Sorry.
Oh, and if you feel your life is in
danger, ask to smoke a cigarette.
We'll come and get you, OK?
- Might buy you more time.
- Yeah, done.
Riley, let's test it.
Say something.
Those Polacks won't give a fuck
if I want to smoke a cigarette.
Sounds great.
All right. Let's stamp it.
All right, it's June 12th, 2017,
at 0500 hours.
This is FBI Special Agent Erica Wilcox.
The following recording will be of
Co-operating Witness 1245-Xray-8
regarding case number 9-Alpha-NY145774.
The recording will be a
consensually-recorded meeting
between CW1245-Xray-8
and Stazek Cusik and Rysard Klimek.
Jeez, guys, a bit obvious
in that damned van!
OK, guys, we got to go. Prius moving.
Let's stop at liquor store.
I want to buy a bottle for my uncle, OK?
My God, this guy has no clue.
Whitey Fisk.
- Whitey Fisk? You know him?
- Yeah. We did time.
- Trust him?
- Yeah, he's a straight guy. Why?
We have a buyer.
We're going to Agnieska Bar.
Wait, wait, wait. What?
What do you mean you got a buyer?
How did you find him?
I checked. He's good.
Fuck!
I really want to see my uncle's face
when we show up with cash.
Jesus Christ!
My cousin's one annoying bitch!
Hook me up!
You don't want any of that.
Her face is a problem, believe me!
He needs to stick to the plan.
He'll fuck everything up.
Are we following to Little Poland?
Guys, there's been a change of plan.
Yes?
Source was ordered to take drugs
to a buyer on his way to Klimek.
OK. If the exchange takes place,
arrest the buyer, recover narcotics.
Copy that.
We follow to Little Poland.
Guys, we follow. You stay close by.
Copy that.
Sit here.
I'll take everything you've got, cabron.
- Whatever we've got?
- Yeah, that's right. All of it.
What are we talking about, hm?
You got a half key or a key?
Six.
Motherfucker! Six keys?
You got a bunch of Polacks walking around
with six fucking keys of Fentanyl?
I fucking love it. You niggas crazy, man.
I ain't got the cash for six but I'm
gonna get that shit, though.
You're not good for six?
No, no, no. I'm good. I'm good for three.
OK, just give me a couple of hours.
I'll bring back the cash. Bam!
Huh?
Relax.
I'm cool, Polack.
You look a little nervous.
What, are you the money guy? Mm?
You guys want the fucking money or not?
- Three keys? That's $85K.
- Yeah, I can fucking count.
You got that in two hours?
I guess you motherfuckers
don't know who the fuck I am.
No, I don't know who you are.
- You did time in Bale Hill?
- That's right.
- Whitey Fisk?
- Yeah. '05 to '09.
- Ah, I did time in Bale Hill.
- Oh, yeah?
Whitey, he was over there in Section 3,
right?
D Section. Right?
They don't got numbers.
They got letters over there.
Who else did you do time with?
Fuck you guys. Fine.
All right, just give me half a key.
I'm good for that right now. Fuck it.
- I thought you said you wanted three.
- Yeah. I want half a key now.
- What the fuck is his problem?
- You didn't answer my question.
- Which question is that?
- Who else did you do time with?
Cantrell and Del Ray.
And go fuck yourself.
- Go fuck myself?
- That's right.
Del Ray, he was murdered.
And Cantrell, he's scratching walls
up in Ulster County Mental,
which means you picked two guys
we can't check on.
What the fuck are you trying to say?
I'm asking you one more time.
How the fuck is a Spic junkie
gonna raise $85K in two hours?
Spic junkie, huh?
You got a nasty fucking mouth,
you know that?
You don't even know me, man.
Are you a cop?
Fuck you. I'm no fucking cop.
- Why the fuck you say that, man?
- You're a cop.
Fuck you.
If these guys find out you're a cop,
you're a dead man. You understand?
Stop saying I'm a fucking cop.
- That's a serious accusation, homie.
- You'll die, I tell you.
- Where you come from?
- I'm a drug dealer, you dumb fuck.
But I don't want to go down
for being a cop killer.
- How far is rescue?
- Five to seven.
Call them. Now.
Moving in, guys. Yeah, now.
Put your money back.
Put your fucking money in your pocket.
Fuck it. You guys don't want my money.
Fuck you, then.
You got one chance.
And I'm gonna give it to you
in a few seconds.
You fucking understand me?
Get the fuck out of here.
Can you believe this fucking guy?
- You waste my time again...
- Whoa.
- I'll fucking kill you.
- Don't fucking touch me. Hey!
- I said get the fuck out of here!
- Don't you fuck... Fuck you! Fuck you!
Waste my time again,
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
Shut the fuck up! Shut the fuck up!
All right?
Yo! Freeze!
Put your fucking hands up!
Hands where I can see them. NYPD.
Chill the fuck out. You too, motherfucker.
- I'm wired, you fuck!
- What?
What the fuck?
Woo-hoo! Burrito on the floor!
Oh, for fuck...
You don't fucking kill cops in New York!
Get some garbage bags.
Come on!
We need to clean this shit.
I got to smoke a cigarette.
Call off rescue.
Let's make this fucking car disappear.
SO's two minutes away.
- You're smoking now?
- A cop just got killed.
- Call them off.
- Calling it off, guys.
What the fuck are you doing here, man?
Come on. I need you inside.
Piotr.
OK.
When did you understand
the buyer was a cop?
Early in the conversation.
I thought he was a rookie who
got into more than he could handle.
I felt he might take advantage
if I gave him an exit.
You thought by kicking
and pushing him to the ground,
he would take advantage
of such polite exit?
I was trying to avoid
a bigger problem for Wojtek.
An NYPD cop just got killed in New York.
Do you know what that means, Piotr?
Bad business.
They will shut down all illegal activities
until they find their cop killer.
Now, Stazek doesn't have documents
because Stazek doesn't exist.
But you?
NYPD will come for you.
The best drug runner in Wojtek.
Oh, Piotr.
This is bad business for me.
- I'm sorry, Mr Klimek.
- Oh, no, don't be sorry.
That feeling doesn't take us anywhere.
We were talking about business here.
Please, sit down.
Stazek tells me that the cop was
pointing the gun in your face. Correct?
So, Stazek saved your life.
You now owe the price of your life
to Wojtek.
How much is your life worth?
I don't know.
Two words.
Closed market.
Bale Hill is a holding unit.
It sends prisoners all over the state.
A hub.
We control the product inside the Hill,
we control the supply to prisons
all over New York.
You did four years at Bale Hill, right?
So, if anyone can get drugs inside,
that's... that's you.
You want me to control the supply inside?
I mean, how would I do that?
Oh, you're a resourceful man.
With Fentanyl, we can have tens
of thousands hooked on our product.
They will work off their debts to Wojtek,
not only in prison
but afterwards on the street.
I will own a fucking army!
You will break your parole.
My lawyers will convince the judge
to send you back to Bale Hill.
With good behaviour,
you'll be released in five years max.
And our debt will be extinguished.
My life ain't worth that much.
How much are the lives of your wife
and daughter worth to you?
We found them, driving around your house.
So frightened.
Suitcase filled with clothes.
You informed them
what happened at Agnieska.
I just told them to get out of the house.
Where were they?
Outside.
Waiting for you.
Oh, don't worry.
Sofia and Anna will be OK
while you're inside.
Now.
Fuck off!
- You safe?
- You guys left me in the fucking lurch.
You were supposed to take us
directly to The General.
I can't call those shots.
I'm only a soldier, I do what I'm told.
Understand?
Only a soldier?
You just brought in six keys for them.
It would've raised suspicion.
They would've stripped me naked.
Meet me tonight and hope
we can salvage something, otherwise
four years of hard work
just went down the fucking drain.
What the fuck you talking about?
Oh, you fucking...
Anna, do you want to come and play?
- Do you want to go play with Nina?
- Look, sweetie...
She's fine. Don't. Now.
I can see you.
- Hi, Nina! You want to play?
- Yeah.
- Go ahead.
- Come on.
Go to the back yard.
Why didn't you do what I told you?
Just one second.
Why didn't you fucking leave?
- Pete, you've blood all over you.
- Answer my question.
Why didn't you protect Anna?
I want to know what's going on.
- Why didn't you protect Anna?
- I'm sorry.
I don't want to hear fucking sorry.
You were supposed to take Anna away. 1pm.
Think they'd have a problem
killing both of you?
Don't talk to me like that! We tried!
We fucking tried!
We kept driving around the block
hoping you'd be back!
Fucking...
Come on.
Driver's licence. It says Carlos Harrera.
His real name was Daniel Gomez.
- Who the fuck are you?
- Detective Edward Grens, Organised Crime.
He was one of mine.
What happened here?
It was supposed to be a low-level buy
off a street tip.
They cut his throat,
pulled out his tongue.
They knew he was a cop.
What did you say his name was?
- Hey!
- Hey.
Thanks for taking me here.
It's so romantic of you.
Yeah. Dig in.
- There real Mogwai meat in these?
- Shut up and eat, girl.
- Homicide talk about anything?
- Like what?
I think Daniel's connection was Polish.
Entire NYPD force on this man hunt.
You don't consider sharing
this little fucking detail?
I got to check my sources before
they get spooked by the stampede.
You heard of Rysard Klimek,
AKA The General?
Polish crime boss, right?
Came over from Poland
after serving 20 years
in some shit-hole
Eastern European dungeon.
Now he's moving pieces
all over the board.
You think he had something
to do with Daniel?
Gomez was killed in this bar
in Little Poland.
It's impossible to trace its owners.
The streets link it to The General.
Security cameras across the street
record Gomez entering at 11:09.
Then, at 11:27, this guy pops out.
Look at his body language.
This is a man who's just done bad.
- What do you need?
- Your badge.
- IA is coming after me.
- Christ. Eddie...
I sent him in when he wasn't ready.
This is on me.
Hold on a second. Watch my six.
That girl over there was Daniel's source.
Shit!
Shit! Help, help, help!
I'll give anyone $20
who stops the puta behind me!
- Help me out, help me out!
- Move! Move!
NYPD! Get the fuck back!
Get back, motherfucker!
- Tell me what happened to Daniel!
- I don't know nothing, OK?
..got Gomez killed, tell me who...
- Like I had something to do with it!
- I know your parents.
Grens, want to talk to me for a second?
Hey, Ed. Hey, Eddie.
You want to talk to me outside?
Ed? Outside? Please, right now, Ed.
You're gonna be down.
What are you doing?
You want to get these motherfuckers?
- Well, this bitch better talk.
- You are scaring the shit out of her.
You want to calm down.
You want to be professional
and let me do this, all right?
- Do what you got to do.
- You stay here.
Hey, honey, you want to
scooch over for a second, please?
Stazek carved him up like that?
You think I'd fucking do that?
I'm just trying to find
a professional way to say this.
- Say what?
- You're fucked, Koslow.
- Wait, who the fuck is he?
- He's my boss.
We tried to close the case on The General
and bury this whole mess.
But Washington labelled the case as weak
and took the embassy off the table.
With all due respect, the fuck you talking
about taking the embassy off the table?
You just watched me smuggle a dozen keys
through Polish diplomatic pouches.
The deal was to give you evidence
to indict The General,
which I have fucking over-delivered
at this point.
Erica, I've done my part.
I want out.
Agent Wilcox here has a plan
to keep your status alive.
You should listen to her
and hope I like it,
cos in my book
you're old news, my friend.
Pete, I think there's a way out of this.
We go along with The General's plan.
Evidence of Fentanyl being methodically
distributed inside a state prison
buries Rysard Klimek for good.
And if that happens,
you're a free man.
What the fuck you talking about?
Going back to prison?
- That was never part of the plan.
- Where's the part of the plan
where you become an accessory to the
murder of an undercover policeman?
How am I an accessory when I tried
to help him? It's all on the tape.
And you guys put me there.
If I inform the NYPD
that I'm working with a witness
to Officer Daniel Gomez's murder,
you will be exposed.
If you're exposed,
The General's case falls apart.
If I say no?
Prosecutor will have you serve the
remaining 12 years of your sentence
and then tack on
whatever the NYPD pins on you.
Some fucking bullshit.
I tried to help him.
You're a convicted felon
who was present when one of their own
was nearly beheaded.
You should think of your family, Pete.
Once you're in charge
like The General wants,
you just build a list of all the inmates
and COs distributing for him.
Every one's a potential nail
to crucify that son of a bitch.
I need to know you're in.
Yeah, let me guess, if I fuck up
in Bale Hill, I'm alone, right?
Don't fuck up.
Once you're in charge
like The General wants,
you just build a list of all the inmates
and COs distributing for him.
Every one's a potential nail
to crucify that son of a bitch.
I need to know you're in.
Yeah, let me guess, if I fuck up
in Bale Hill, I'm alone, right?
Don't fuck up.
Yeah.
Thank you.
All right. Thank you.
Yeah. Thank you. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
OK. Got a couple of hits on the names.
First a Pole. Street name Stazek.
Real name unknown.
Whereabouts unknown.
Unfortunately that's it on him.
He was probably recently imported.
- Well, what about the American?
- This is where it gets interesting.
Peter Koslow. He's uh...
- What?
- Complex.
Born here.
Parents emigrated from Poland.
Gulf War vet. Sniper.
Served an additional four tours in Iraq.
post-traumatic stress disorder.
Crashed and burned a few years ago.
Manslaughter.
Got 20 years for killing a guy
in a bar fight. Then it's weird.
Weird how?
Well, the file looks like
it's been redacted.
Paroled from Bale Hill after four, pending
the full investigation of new evidence.
Doesn't add up, though.
Who could
fuck with his jacket like that?
Feds is my guess.
Can you dig into this Fed angle?
You can't fucking poke around the Feds
like one of your junkie hookers, Grens.
I think this is the guy who shot Daniel.
You said Bale Hill, right? Bale Hill
was part of Daniel's cover story.
He liked it because his old man
served time there.
But that was years ago.
If this guy was fresh out, he could've
tripped the kid up on something.
Let me see what I can do.
Shit!
Got a breakfast date with my sweetheart.
Wait, this guy you're running to,
is it somebody special?
Are you jealous?
I'm just hoping his name ain't
fucking Logan, or Chad, or Brett!
Laila. Her name is Laila.
Laila?
Cat, why didn't you tell me that?
Lai... Yo!
I should come with you and Laila.
Y'all want a chaperone?
- What are you doing here?
- We have to talk. Important stuff.
Don't come knocking at my fucking door.
Go to the garage.
All night awake. Fuck!
What happened?
We had to do some sweeping.
The guy you did time with.
- Whitey?
- Yeah, Whitey.
We found him 30 minutes ago.
Why don't you fucking listen to me?
I told you the cop just used his name.
He's a straight guy.
You can complain to my uncle.
He wants to see you.
- Your wife a good cook?
- Why?
It's an old tradition -
you invite boss home before prison.
Use a little of this
to break your parole.
The rest enters Bale Hill.
Yeah, I still got to figure out a way.
Figure it out fast, Piotr.
A detective is sniffing around
Little Poland.
Monday, you need to be inside.
Kalash told me you went out last night,
motherfucker.
- Where did you go?
- That's none of your fucking business.
Come on.
I want to know, where did you go?
My wife's next door.
You have kurwa?
She a good fuck?
Who is she?
Come on, tell me. You mind if I bang her
while you're inside?
You touch any of my things
when I'm inside
and I'll carve your fucking eyes out.
When?
Tomorrow? In a month?
Two days.
If you go back inside,
you'll never get out.
You know that, do you?
You happy to spend the day with Daddy?
Mm-hm.
What are you doing?
You see that down there? That's where
I'll be going on my business trip.
But I don't want you to go.
I know, sweetie, but what if I told you
this was the last time?
Gotta go.
New warden's name
is James Leinart. He's been briefed.
You give him the list,
he'll put you in solitary.
In 24 hours, the Appellate Court Judge
will put you back on the streets.
Daddy, you're too loud.
Can't hear my movie.
I know. I'm sorry, sweetie.
Here, just watch a movie.
Sofia and Anna
will be in an FBI safe house
before Klimek even knows what happened.
You have my absolute word on that.
Look, I... I'm gonna need three favours.
First, I need a major drugs sweep
the day after I get there,
to dry up the competition.
Second, have Warden Leinart
put me on programme Post Detail.
And third, in six days...
..courier these beautiful yellow wonders
to Deputy Superintendent Rasheeda Johnson,
compliments of the Bureau.
So the prison
receives them on Founders' Day
- with a Government seal on the package.
- I can't do this, Pete.
You know, if the Prosecutor finds out
that I helped people get high,
he'll destroy me, you and the case.
You got to fucking help me out here.
I can't do it.
It won't come through
if it don't come from you guys.
All right.
Have Leinart assign me
to roof and yard maintenance.
That I'll do.
The drugs sweep I'll also do.
But the rest, you're on your own.
How's Sofia holding up?
Just fucking great.
- I'm sorry, I got to take this.
- Yeah.
One second, boss.
I got to go.
You'll be fine.
Piotr!
Pete, you should have told me
we had friends coming tonight.
They brought me so many presents to
keep me comfortable while you're away.
You have such an adorable wife, Piotr.
- Beata. Nice to meet you.
- Pleased to meet you.
We should get this little creature
in bed, then we can celebrate.
Let's go. I will help.
- It's OK, I got it.
- No, no, no, please.
Piotr, I insist.
After you.
I don't have kids, Piotr. I regret it.
Must be wonderful.
It is.
Beata wants them, but I'm afraid.
I would suffer too much
if something happened to them.
Imagine someone hurts them.
In the honour of bravery of Pete,
his courageous wife,
here is a Polish song
entitled I Used To Be A Rose.
It talks about the love
we give to our partners.
Na zdrowie.
- Na zdrowie.
Yeah. You need more reason to dig?
The General just left
the Koslow residence.
- You want to go to the zoo or not?
- Let's go to the zoo. Come on!
- We'll be back in a couple of hours.
- OK.
- Be a good girl, OK?
- Be good!
- You know Daddy loves you very much.
- I know.
- Can I go now?
- I know, right.
- Anna, come on!
- Pete... Pete, come on.
- Let's go, Anna.
- Give me a kiss!
- See you later, guys.
- Bye.
- Have fun!
Send me photos!
Those kids with the drone.
Better call them today.
Pete, don't worry.
I don't want you to worry.
I'll take care of it.
- You still got the key?
- It's right here.
It's gonna be fine.
911. What's your emergency?
Please! I need help!
My husband's going crazy!
He wants to kill me!
Please send someone fast!
Ma'am? All right.
- Do you have any children in the house?
- Please send someone fast!
Second time round, huh?
I want you to stand right there for me.
Oh, what language is that?
I don't know. I was drunk when I did it.
Could be Chinese or something.
Not going to tell me, huh?
OK, now show me your arms.
- Are you affiliated?
- He is.
Last term he became a courier
on behalf of the Poles.
True. Gave you the white shirt, Slewitt.
- His bed been assigned?
- Not yet.
I got this.
Welcome back, Koslow.
Let 'em know he's here.
Follow me.
Stand right there.
OK.
I see ya.
I see ya, boy.
Hey, you in my pen, you see me talking
to you. Don't walk away from me.
- Morning.
- Morning, boss.
Morning, gentlemen.
One time, one time.
Wake up, sleepyhead!
Hey, big man!
Carlos.
Yo, fellas!
Looks like we got us a new white boy.
- What up, Slewitt?
- Smiley, this is Koslow. Your new celly.
- Try to make him feel at home.
- Hey, what? What?
Hey, don't be scared. They'll be gentle.
Won't you, boys?
The prodigal son returns.
I need two extra beds.
You and you, roll it up.
It's your lucky day, dickheads,
you're moving into South.
Each and every business that takes place
under the roof of this facility
runs through me.
Comply or I crucify you.
- Get back to your block.
- Yes, sir.
Rise and shine, ladies!
Backs against the wall!
It's time to get the fuck up!
Name?
Koslow, P.
Pervious term you kept yourself busy.
Roofing, HVAC maintenance.
We should get you on a programme,
Mr Koslow.
I'd appreciate that, Warden.
Name?
That guy.
- This guy.
- Arms up. Legs spread.
Next.
You.
- This dumb fuck.
- Legs spread.
They've swept the whole place, kumpel.
Bone dry.
That's a lucky break for us.
Product will be here soon.
Hand under table.
- Who?
- K-O-S-L-O-W.
Comma, Peter.
- I'm sorry, I don't...
- Oh, don't apologise.
Me, I'm old school - a "knock on doors,
get right there in your face" type of cop.
Wilcox, we got to go.
I'm sorry. You are?
Detective Edward Grens from the NYPD.
- Everything good?
- Yeah.
We're just having a conversation
about somebody named Peter Koslow.
Decorated vet,
driver-slash-security
for the Polish consulate.
Fast-tracked on what smells like a bogus
parole violation back into Bale Hill.
The same prison he was serving
20 years for murder
before somebody pulled him out
pending the investigation
of new evidence.
Anyway, I want to know
why your subordinate's name
keeps popping up around this admittedly
suspicious motherfucking file.
I'm sure that Agent Wilcox's name pops up
on a number of case files, Detective.
You should check with the DEA.
They just sent me here.
Look, if I was involved
in the kind of pro-active operation
that you are suggesting, I would be
intimately acquainted with uh...
Peter... what was his name again?
- Koslow.
Our organisations may not see eye-to-eye,
Detective.
But we have extended you every
professional courtesy we can.
There's Koslow.
Right after Gomez was killed.
That Prius screaming "We're the FBI",
that's you all leaving the scene.
And here, even though this picture
may be hard to read,
that person looks very much like you,
Agent Wilcox,
driving away from the crime scene.
You want to pitch
your field office against
the biggest police department
in the world, let's do it.
We love us a good fight.
Have a good day.
What perfume you wear?
It smells expensive.
All right,
let's get this shit cleaned up.
Clean that shit up.
It must be tough on you.
- We'll get through it.
- Like you did the last time.
I checked the old visitor logs
at Bale Hill.
You and Anna
never missed a visitor's day.
That's how you kept him strong, huh?
You let him see how much he had to lose.
- What do you want?
- Someone killed a friend of mine.
I used to think your husband did it.
But now I'm not so sure.
This FBI thing
has got me thinking otherwise.
Look, I'm here to help your husband.
But you got to give me something
to work with.
You know, five years ago,
we walked into a bar,
looking for a jumpstart for our car.
Some bikers inside started
making comments about me,
so Pete asked them to stop.
And then he was fighting three of them.
That night, I went from being
the wife of a great father,
and a loving husband,
to the wife of a convict killer.
And since then,
every time someone tells us
they want to help,
they end up doing the exact opposite.
So, unless you want to buy something,
with all due respect to you and the NYPD,
get the fuck out of my store.
I'm not like all the others, Mrs Koslow.
I hope you don't learn that the hard way.
Stay safe out here.
And here we go.
Over here!
- Box out. Box out.
- I got it. I got it. I got it.
Let him through.
Knicks hardly get that exciting, huh?
Who's this?
Motherfucker, I'm the Hangman.
And I just put a tight noose
around your neck.
In a few hours,
you're gonna be alone on this yard.
It will be the scariest moment
of your life.
Your only way out is that man
in front of you.
His name is Vermin.
When you're ready to talk
about Officer Gomez's murder,
tell Vermin to call the Hangman.
Here I am, dead man.
Present and fucking accounted for.
We need to talk.
I got a fucking present for you.
Why you selling fucking product
on my patch?
To get your attention.
You have it. But I don't think
it's something you want.
- Slewitt!
- Agh!
That's for not respecting the system.
That's for not following my rules.
Midas! Midas! Midas, listen,
listen, listen! Please, listen!
You got to listen to me!
I'm here to take out The General.
And his... And his Bale Hill
distribution chain.
I need all the names.
I'll take them down.
I'll fucking help you.
Make it look like it's a suicide.
Clean up after you've done.
Klimek is importing six keys
of Fentanyl per week.
What are those names for?
I'm a... I'm a snitch.
I'm a snitch.
Lay him down.
It's their fault, then.
Hey, you all right, dead man?
You're a snitch?
I made a deal with the Feds
to take down The General.
You're on top now.
But The General's
coming for you harder than ever.
If you give me that list,
I'll bury that Polish cocksucker.
That's all.
So what's it gonna be?
If you're alive in three hours...
..you'll fucking know my answer.
You can wait here.
Grens went to Bale Hill.
Shit.
I'm sure Leinart blocked him.
He did, but it's only a matter of time
before he gets to Koslow.
He's already got Washington
on the fucking phone,
asking me why a NYPD cop
is trying to subpoena a file
on an FBI informant who shouldn't exist.
Look, we just need to stall a few days.
Koslow is so close to delivering,
and then it won't matter.
What? What are you thinking?
- Burn him.
- No.
He has a family.
I mean, you can't make this call.
The Bureau can't afford the luxury
of your precious feelings right now.
We looked him in the eyes.
We made him guarantees.
You took a convicted killer
out of prison,
ran him off the books and stuck him
in a room where a cop was murdered.
If you don't see how this is
about to blow the fuck up,
and tear you apart with it,
you're not the agent I thought you were.
How fucking dare you?
I was operating under your authority.
You will not throw me under the fucking
bus if I don't burn an innocent man.
I don't have to throw you under the bus.
I didn't know anything
about this operation.
You were trying to impress a superior
and you went too far.
We'll make an example of you.
You will serve jail time.
I guarantee it.
You know, I started on this floor
23 years ago.
My desk was right there.
Burn him.
It's an order.
I had you, white boy.
Smiley Phelps was right behind you.
Like a nigga-inja.
Hey, Warden. I want to shake your hand.
- Come on, leave the Warden alone.
- No, no, it's OK.
I just want to thank you and congratulate
you for running this place the right way.
I'm now requesting solitary.
I can't do that, Pete.
You leave me out here,
I'm a fucking dead man.
I'm sorry, Pete. They were very clear.
Who was clear? Look, this wasn't the deal.
Just get Wilcox here right now.
- Escort the inmate back to his block.
- Yes, sir.
Leinart! Leinart! Come back here!
Come on.
Time is up.
Come on, guys. Get off the phones.
Next in line. Six minutes.
Wilcox.
It's me.
You get it? I drew you the picture.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I did what you told me. I drew the
picture. And now I need to show it to you.
I need to show it to you right now.
You promised you'd come see it.
You fucking promised.
Are you there?
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Hey, how much time I got?
Two minutes and 15 seconds.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Pete?
Are you OK?
The key. You got to use it right now.
Why?
They fucked me.
- I'm not getting out of this.
- No. No.
Just shut up. You listen to me.
There is a detective.
He... He asked about the dead cop.
He knows about the FBI.
OK? You don't fucking give up now!
OK. All right. Give him the tapes.
Tell him there's information about Gomez.
He'll know what to do.
But you got to make him promise
to protect you too.
You got to do it now.
You and Anna ain't safe.
You got to get out of the house right now.
OK, babe? You got to get
out of the house right now. Promise me.
Promise me, right now, OK?
- Now.
- I promise.
Time is up!
Pete!
I have some information that might
interest your biggest client.
Move away from that box.
Sit on the chair.
How did you find me?
Your phone. We heard everything.
We tracked you here.
Now...
You and Anna need to get off the grid.
You need to go somewhere
the Poles won't find you.
Take those tapes,
and get the fuck out of our lives.
What the fuck you talking about?
Going back to prison?
That was never part of the plan.
How am I an accessory when I tried
to help him? It's all on the tape.
And you guys put me there.
If I inform the NYPD I'm working with a
witness to Officer Daniel Gomez's murder,
you will...
I was always close by, Pete. I was
never gonna let anything happen to you.
How's Sofia holding up?
Look how scared my daughter is.
She's stopped trusting me again.
Sofia and Anna
will be in an FBI safe house
before Klimek even knows what happened.
You have my absolute word on that.
Against the pack.
Oh, and it was a front pass.
Get the fuck back. Stay the fuck back.
Stay back.
Armed back-up required, ASAP.
Back the fuck off.
Everybody on your knees!
Face the wall! Hands on the wall!
- Back the fuck up!
- On your knees! Face the wall!
Hands on the wall!
Stay there or I run this through
his brain. Back the fuck up!
- Just take it easy.
- Talk to your boys.
- Don't do anything stupid.
- Get the fuck back! Back up!
I will kill him right now!
Back the fuck off!
Do what the fuck he says!
Stay away from him.
Stay down there.
Get the fuck away!
Get the fuck down there!
OK.
Get over there or
I jam this in his fucking brain.
Hear what I'm saying?
Get the fuck over there!
I will fucking kill him right here.
- Back the fuck up!
- It's all right.
You tell Leinart
I want to talk to the press.
I want a phone to call my wife.
He's got 15 minutes
or I fucking kill this guy.
- Take it easy.
- Give me the keys.
Stay there.
You stay right there.
- What colour?
- Black.
- What colour's the next one?
- Uh... blue.
You fucking...
I think we should put um, the...
Girls, don't leave the bikes outside.
Take them in the back yard.
Come on. Tea's almost ready.
Hi.
You're so sweet.
Anna!
Anna! Come with me!
Get the...
What the fuck are you doing here?
Go inside! Go inside!
Get away from us!
Go on! Go on!
Fuck you!
Ms Koslow?
Ms Koslow? Is that you?
Surprise.
Ms Koslow!
Everything's ready, sir.
Hey.
I just got word from Leinart
that Koslow has taken a hostage.
He wants to talk to the press.
I know.
ADIC has granted me his authority.
I'm going out there.
This ends now.
NYPD, freeze!
Where are they?
Stand up.
Anna! No!
Don't take my daughter!
Shut up, or I'm gonna kill her.
Shut up!
Now, we're gonna play a game. OK?
Where is he?
Where's our friend?
There he is.
Sit down.
I will cut your tongue out
like I did with your friend.
Attention. Federal authorities
are superseding local chains of command.
Federal authorities are superseding
local chains of command.
Federal authorities are coming in.
Paramedic! Move! Move! Move!
Moving into position.
Surrender to the authorities.
Hey, Pete?
Pete?
It's only me.
Everything's cool.
I got the phone
so you can call your wife.
Welcome. Ray Barnes. HRT Supervisor.
Bring me up to date. Where are we?
Inmate Koslow is holding CO Slewitt
up there in the HVAC room.
We have three shooters in position.
One to the North.
We got two more. South and East Towers.
They're the only ones with eyes.
What decision do I need to make
in the next five minutes?
Well, right now, we're buying time.
Breach will be through in 15 minutes.
HN's still stuck in traffic.
Leinart has given Koslow one of our phones
to call his family.
- If he calls the press, cut the call.
- Copy that.
- Yes?
- Hey, Sofia. It's me.
Baby, what's happening?
- Are you safe?
- Tell me what's happening.
Everything's going to be all right,
sweetheart. I'm just...
I got this. Don't worry.
- Are you and Anna safe?
- Yes. We're safe. We're safe.
Um... Anna's here. You want to talk to her?
- All right, put her on.
- Yes.
Talk to your daddy.
Are you coming home, Daddy?
I'm trying, my love.
I'm trying. It's just uh...
I got held up here, but uh...
Please, Daddy. Come back home.
I'm scared.
I'm trying, my love. I'm doing everything
I can to get home to you as soon as I can.
I just... I just want to tell you that...
..Daddy loves you very much.
I love you very much.
Cut the call.
Put Mommy back on.
- Pete?
- Babe...
I have a visual of inmate
with a shiv at the officer's throat.
Reds, what you got?
Zero movement, sir.
- Three?
- Negative, sir. I've lost the visual.
Slewitt. Wake up.
Hey.
God damn it, what the fuck is he doing?
Come on.
What the fuck?
There you go.
Come on!
Let's see what you got!
Red Three, you have the shot?
Negative. No clean strike.
Repeat, no clean strike.
I have a clean shot.
Repeat, I have a clean shot.
- Hostage clear.
- You're clear hot.
Aagh!
We got a survivor.
They got somebody. Let's go!
- Give me an ID on the survivor.
- I need an ID on the survivor.
Slewitt.
S-L-E-W-I-T-T.
Well done, Agent Wilcox.
Good job.
- Get the door!
- Coming through!
Go! Go!
All right. Move it out.
All right, we're loaded.
Move it up.
I'm coming with you.
First- and
second-degree murder. ETA, eight minutes.
Here. Cuff yourself to his leg.
Here's your change.
I recognised him on the stretcher.
Where is he?
- In a motel, upstate.
- Address?
If you shield me from the OPR
investigation on the Gomez murder.
You think I'm here to negotiate?
Who else knows about this?
- You and me.
- You need to fix this.
No one can save you from the Gomez
investigation while Koslow is alive.
Sunny Side Motel,
Northern Ave, Murray Hill.
Room?
304.
You know what to do.
I can't.
- If you can't, I will.
- Keith, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, Keith.
ASAC Montgomery?
I'm Special Agent Barbara Lee with OPR.
We've a federal warrant
for your arrest.
Please put your hands behind your back,
thumbs together.
Yeah, we have our target in custody.
Meet us at Pier 11, Wall Street.
Don't it just warm your heart to see the
FBI and the NYPD finally co-operate?
Koslow. This is from Wilcox.
She couldn't get rid of the tail
on your family.
We need you to lay low for another month
till it gets worked out with
the corrupt prison investigation
the FBI's conducting.
She promises you're
gonna see your family soon.
But you need to go now
before they catch you.
Subtitles by Deluxe